<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<COMMITTEE>
  <STEERING>
    <BODY>The Head of this committee shall be a final year senator and members from 2nd and 3rd Year selected by the head and ratified by the senate.</BODY>
	
    <AIM>
	<i>It shall be responsible for publishing and circulating the minutes of Students’ Council and Students’ Senate meeting.</i>
	<ii>It shall work in coordination with authorities to communicate with students body regarding important information (Notices, Fest Invitations etc.)</ii>
	<iii>It shall maintain record of the applications submitted.</iii>
	<iv>It shall publish a semester report of the functioning of Students' Council.</iv>
	
	</AIM>
	
  </STEERING>
   
   <HOSTELAFFAIRS>
   <BODY>
   The Head of this committee shall be a final year senator and members from 2nd and 3rd Year selected by the head and ratified by the senate
   </BODY>
    <AIM>
	<i>This committee shall keep in touch with authorities to suggest measures to improve Academics related activities (Library, Departmental Library, Educational Tours, and Placements etc.)</i>
	<ii>This committee shall play an advisory role in academics affairs</ii>
	</AIM>
   </HOSTELAFFAIRS>
    
   <ACADEMICAFFAIRS>
   <BODY>The Head of this committee shall be a final year senator and members from 2nd and 3rd Year selected by the head and ratified by the senate</BODY>
    <AIM>
	<i>It shall prepare a monthly report of each hostel and submit it to DSW, Chief Warden and Warden</i>
	<ii>It shall suggest measures to Warden and Chief Warden to improve Hostel functioning and amenities</ii>
	
	<iii>It could call meetings with hostel committees to improve coordination</iii>
	
	<iv>It shall contact Warden and Chief Warden if hostel committees are found to be inactive</iv>
	
	</AIM>
   </ACADEMICAFFAIRS>
   
   <CAMPUSAMENITIES>
   <BODY>The Head of this committee shall be a final year senator and members from 2nd and 3rd Year selected by the head and ratified by the senate</BODY>
    <AIM>
	<i>i.	It shall suggest DSW and Chairman, Campus Amenities regarding necessary amenities to be provided in campus</i>
	<ii>ii.	It shall look after amenities provided in the campus and inform DSW and Chairman, Campus Amenities in case of poor facilities</ii>
	
	</AIM>
   </CAMPUSAMENITIES>
   
   <DISCIPLINE>
   <BODY>
   i.	The Head of this committee shall be a     final year senator and members from 2nd and 3rd Year selected by the head and ratified by the senate. 
ii.	Members suggested by technical affairs to be ratified by Proctor.

   </BODY>
    <AIM>
	<i>It shall be help in maintaining Discipline and Decorum of the Institute</i>
	
	<li>ii.	It shall report to proctor in cases of indiscipline</li>
	<iii>
	Members selected from technical affairs shall help in maintaining discipline during Techniti (Technical Festival of NIT Jalandhar)
	</iii>
	</AIM>
   </DISCIPLINE>
   	
</COMMITTEE>